export const introPythonAssignment = {
  title: 'Introduction to Python â€“ Assignment',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Which of the following is true about Python?',
      options: [
        'Python is hard to learn',
        'Python is platform dependent',
        'Python is interpreted',
        'Python uses brackets for blocks',
      ],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Who developed Python?',
      options: [
        'James Gosling',
        'Dennis Ritchie',
        'Guido van Rossum',
        'Ken Thompson',
      ],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Which symbol starts a comment in Python?',
      options: ['//', '#', '/*', '--'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Python supports which programming style?',
      options: [
        'Procedural',
        'Object-Oriented',
        'Functional',
        'All of the above',
      ],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Python is widely used in?',
      options: [
        'Web development',
        'Data science',
        'Automation',
        'All of the above',
      ],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Indentation in Python is used for?',
      options: [
        'Decoration',
        'Looping',
        'Code blocks',
        'Comments',
      ],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Which file extension is used for Python?',
      options: ['.pt', '.pyt', '.py', '.python'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Python is suitable for beginners because?',
      options: [
        'Simple syntax',
        'Large community',
        'Readable code',
        'All',
      ],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Python programs are executed _____',
      options: [
        'Line by line',
        'After compilation',
        'As machine code',
        'Randomly',
      ],
      correctIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Python helps in building?',
      options: [
        'Logic',
        'Problem-solving skills',
        'Programming foundation',
        'All',
      ],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
  ],
}